ceo.com 2017-09-16

# CEO.com Privacy Policy | CEO.com

**Last Updated:   February 1, 2013 **

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the CEO.com website and services (the “Site”). The Site is owned and operated by CEO.com, LLC, a Utah limited liability company (“CEO.com, LLC”).

**Summary**  
Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on the Site and the web. We use aggregated (gathered up data across all user accounts) information to develop content targeted to users’ interests and to better Site user experience. We are committed to your privacy and, other than as provided herein or after receiving your specific consent, we will not share any personal information with any third party at any time, unless required by law.

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy covers only the Site and activities of CEO.com, LLC related to the Site. This privacy policy does not apply to other websites owned or controlled by CEO.com, LLC or our activities associated with those websites.

Please be aware that sponsors, advertisers and partners or affiliates with co-branded modules or sections on the Site may collect personally identifiable information about you while on the Site. The information practices of those parties are not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by us through the Site.

Site users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in blogs, chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Gathering of Information**

**Voluntary Submission**  
We do not collect personally identifiable information about any individual Site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information, such as your e-mail address, title and industry when you register for or subscribe to the Site or sign up for certain features or offerings available from the Site. You may also provide information to us in other contexts, including, for example, in order to enter into a sweepstakes or promotion through the Site. In the event you order something from the Site, we may request additional personal information, such as your address, telephone number and credit card information, in order to complete the purchase. We also supplement the data you provide to us with data from data append services. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain features of the Site. When you register for or subscribe to the Site or provide information to the Site in any other manner, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information.

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

_Cookies_  
Cookies are files that web servers place on an Internet user’s computer that are designed to store basic information (such as visitor preferences). The use of cookies on the Site allows visitors to enjoy more seamless visits and more accurately measures visitor behavior on the Site. There are two types of cookies that we may use: session and persistent. Session cookies exist only during an Internet user’s online session. They disappear from the user’s computer when he/she closes the browser software. Persistent cookies remain on the user’s computer after the browser has been closed. The cookies used on the Site do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser, unless you choose to identify yourself voluntarily. You may choose to identify yourself for any one of the following reasons or other reasons: by asking the browser to remember your username and password, by responding to a promotional offer, or by personalizing a web page or requesting more information on a product or service.

When you interact with the Site, we strive to make that experience easy, meaningful, and relevant. When you come to the Site, our web server uses cookies to improve your interaction with the Site by, for example, remembering your preferences and dynamically serving more relevant content to you. More specifically, we use cookies to measure your behavior on the Site and to save personal settings on specific pages. For subscribers who login to the Site, cookies can also be used to save the username so that we can process the saved login information and quickly log that user into the Site. Cookies also help us make sure you are who you say you are after you’ve logged in. We may link personal information that you have submitted on the Site with our cookies that are associated with your visit(s) to the Site in order to provide more relevant content to you during your visit(s). We use cookies (that only we can read and use) to identify the fact that you are one of our subscribers or a prior Site visitor (as applicable). Visitors who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will still be able to browse the Site; however, they may lose some of the functionality provided by the use of cookies.

Business partners of CEO.com, LLC, vendors providing hosting and other services for CEO.com, LLC, third party analytics providers, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements on the Site may set their own unique cookies through your browser. We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain. If you would like more information about this practice and about your option not to accept cookies placed by these companies, please click [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, choose to accept cookies only from certain websites or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from the Site, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site. To learn more about the use of cookies in online advertising including how to manage or delete them click [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

_Web Beacons_  
We use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) on the Site in order to recognize users, assess traffic patterns, identify preferred content and measure site engagement. We also include web beacons in our e-mail messages, including newsletters, in order to count how many e-mail messages have been opened.

CEO.com, LLC also uses a reputable third party to collect information, including through the use of web beacons, browser cookies and other tracking technologies. We may collect via web beacons various data provided by your browser while you are on the Site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a 3rd party. This data is collected in the aggregate, but may include or be associated with other non-personally identifiable information or personally identifiable information that users have voluntarily submitted.

**Use of Information**

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on the Site and to improve the Site.

**To Target Content and Advertising**  
To develop and provide content and advertising to you that is targeted to your interests, we use the analytics collected by the systems described above to determine which areas of the Site you prefer based upon the frequency of your visits and engagement with those areas. We may make reasonable assumptions based on your browser-provided data to target relevant content and advertising to you on the Site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a 3rd party. We may also make reasonable geographic and demographic assumptions based on your presented IP address to target relevant content and advertising.

**To Provide Interactive Communications From CEO.com**  
To enhance your experience we may provide you with interactive communications, such as our electronic newsletters, to the e-mail address that you provide to us. From time to time we may also provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the Site.

**To Provide Communications From Third Parties**  
We respect the privacy of users of the Site and will not, with the exception of related or associated entities and certain specifically designated affiliates and business partners, disclose or distribute our user list to any third party for their own use, nor will we authorize anyone else to do so. We may also provide you with communications from third party affiliates and business partners, which we will send on their behalf without disclosing your email address to them.

**Control of Your Information**  
You may elect to stop receiving newsletters or marketing material from the Site or on behalf of external third party business partners by following instructions at the end of any such e-mail received.

**Sharing of Information**  
We use third party service providers to provide automated data processing, marketing automation, data appends, contact discovery, delivery and other services on the Site, as well as to provide various services to or for us.  When you sign up for certain of our services, we may share your personally identifiable information as necessary for one or more third parties to provide that service.  These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

We may disclose personal information when required by law, or in order to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on the Site or to protect and defend the rights of CEO.com, LLC. Certain personal information that we collect on the Site may be distributed among ourselves or other third parties solely for the purposes of processing your request or arranging delivery of the content, product, or service that you have requested. We may store and process personal information in the United States or any other country in which we (or any of our agents) maintain facilities.

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on the Site or request feedback from you regarding the Site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you, such as your name and e-mail. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use this personally identifiable information to notify contest winners and award prizes and as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

We also have features that allow you to send an e-mail to yourself and/or others about an item on the Site. If you choose to use our e-mail referral service, you will be required to provide the e-mail address or addresses that will be used in the notification. Upon form submission an e-mail will be generated to your recipient(s) inviting them to visit the URL you have recommended. We use this information for the purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and may also store it and use it for other purposes described in this privacy policy.

**Aggregate, Anonymous Information With Advertisers**  
We derive revenue from advertising and sharing information to help us provide the services that are available through the Site. In order to attract and retain advertisers we use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We do not disclose personally identifiable information about our users to these parties.

**International Visitors**

Users from outside the United States should be aware that they are submitting their information to servers within the United States and that they may not be entitled to protections and remedies provided under laws of their places of residence. By providing personal information to us, you consent to the transfer of it to the United States and the use of it in accordance with this privacy policy.

**In The Event of Sale or Bankruptcy**

The ownership of CEO.com, LLC and/or the Site may change at some point in the future. Should that occur, we want this site to be able to maintain a relationship with you. In the event of a sale, merger, public offering, bankruptcy or other change in control of CEO.com, LLC and/or the Site, your information may be shared with the person or business that owns or controls the Site. Opting out of receiving information from third parties will not affect our right to transfer your information to a new owner, but your choices will continue to be respected regarding the use of your information. You will be notified as described below in “How will I know if the Privacy Policy is changed.”

**Privacy of Children** ****

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as a Site user.  If you are under 13, you are not allowed to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address.   If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at privacy@CEO.com.

**Security**

The Site has physical, administrative and technical measures in place to maintain the security, confidentiality, and integrity of the data under our control, and to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of such data. While we strive to protect your personal information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure and therefore we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you send to us. You send any information via the Site at your own risk.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at privacy@CEO.com.

**How Will I Know if the Privacy Policy Is Changed?**

This privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Any material changes to our privacy policy will be posted to this privacy policy, the Site home page, and other places we deem appropriate.
